You always act this way.
This is why I could never get over you.
While we're waiting for our divorce,
I can sleep with you all the time, right?
There are many more things we can do
to make it look like
we really love each other.
Then do it all.
What exactly are you making?
Mom!
Please stop. Mom will get us wrong.
Open the door now!
You need to back off a little, Ging.
If I did, that would mean
I've lost to that brat.
Yes, Mom?
I'm feeling a little dizzy.
Can you take me to the hospital, Runch?
Sure. I'll be right over.
My mom's not feeling well.
I have to go check on her,
so I might be home late.
I bet that old hag's faking it.
- Mom? Where are you? Are you okay?
- Runch is here now.
Forget about the hospital.
I'm feeling better now.
Right. Runch, do you remember Maylin?
- Maylin…?
- Maylinya.
She is Samorn's daughter.
You two had lots of play dates
when you were little.
I remember her now. Maylin.
It's been a while.
It sure has.
I didn't think I'd see you again so soon.
She just got back from the US
two days ago.
Right. Since you're already here,
why don't you join us for dinner?
She's got a lot to talk about with you.
She works in the legal field too.
Please? Pretty please?
Sure, Mom.
- Help yourself, honey.
- Thank you.
She's starting a new job next week,
so she wants your advice.
Sure thing, Maylin.
It takes great attention to detail
to work in the legal field.
And more importantly,
you must treat your clients as humans,
not cases.
Sometimes, the things they don't say
matter more than what they do say.
Well said, Runch.
I'm glad to see you again.
If you don't mind,
can I add you so we can text?
Of course.
Here you go.
Done.
Thank you.
Dig in, Runch.
Sure.
Neen.
Neen, can you open the door for me?
I'm home.
What is it?
I see you've bought me dinner.
What? Who bought you dinner? I didn't.
But they're all my favorite dishes.
You were waiting
to have dinner with me, right?
No, I wasn't. Why would I?
I have no reason to.
Here.
Here's your appetizer.
I'm not hungry.
Your stomach just protested, though.
I told you I'm not hungry.
Don't be upset and hangry now.
Let's go downstairs and eat.
Either come downstairs,
or I'll carry you.
Your choice.
Here we go.
- Fried rice. Nice and hot.
- Thank you.
- Go ahead.
- May I?
Dig in.
You must be hungry.
So how's your mother?
She has high blood pressure.
High blood pressure?
She called you just for that?
Well, at first,
I was going to take her to the hospital.
That means you didn't.
Why not?
She's feeling better now,
so I didn't need to.
I knew it.
She was faking it.
She just wanted you to go see her.
You always fall for her tricks.
She's my mom.
Either way, I had to go check on her
so I could rest easy.
Sure.
What a wonderful daughter you are.
Let's eat.
Aren't you going to read that text?
No.
Because I'm having dinner
with you right now.
I don't care about anything else.
Okay.
Okay, Mom.
Tomorrow's my day off,
so I'll come right over.
Sure. Talk to you later. Okay.
Where are you going, Neen?
My mom said my grandparents miss me.
She told me to visit them
whenever I'm free,
so I'm thinking I'll go tomorrow.
Perfect. I've missed them.
Can I come with?
Who invited you?
I'm going alone.
I don't think that's a good idea.
What if they ask about me?
What will you tell them?
That we're getting divorced?
They'd be crushed.
Let's go together.
- So it's settled. I'm off to work now.
- No, Runch.
Runch!
What are you doing?
I'm doing the packing for you.
Mind your own business, will you?
It's my stuff. I can do it myself.
I just wanted you
to feel as relaxed as you can.
Thank you. But please don't do it again.
I'll still do it for you
because I know you always
forget something when you pack.
That's not true. I know how to pack.
But…
I do forget sunscreen sometimes.
That's exactly why I had to pack for you.
How nice.
What was that?
Nothing.
Oh?
Go pack for yourself. I'm going to shower.
What if
I want to shower with you?
No. Get out already.
- Go.
- I'm not done yet.
I can pack for myself. Just go shower.
Are you sure you can?
Are you free to talk, Maylin?
I wanted to invite you over for lunch
since it's the weekend.
Runch will be here too.
You're coming, right?
Once the food's been delivered,
I'll call you right away.
Thanks.
Who's this Maylin?
Oh.
It's Samorn's daughter. Remember her?
We used to see her when she was little.
Ah. I remember now.
She's the cute little girl
who always followed Runch around.
- Yeah.
- Isn't she studying abroad?
She was, but she just got back recently.
She came to see me yesterday
and gave me a souvenir
as soon as she got back.
How sweet of her.
She has such a pretty face and body.
And she's well-mannered too.
What a shame.
What do you mean?
It's a shame
she and Runch didn't meet sooner.
I would've asked her
to marry our daughter.
How can you think that?
Why can't I? It's just a thought.
Well, I sure hope so.
Don't do anything immoral.
What do you mean?
Don't break up a couple. I'm warning you.
You know me too well.
But I'm not afraid of sinning.
I'd better call Runch.
MOM
Answer it, or your mom
will just keep calling all day.
- Yes, Mom?
- Runch,
please join me for lunch today.
I can't today.
What? Where are you going?
Are you busy all day or something?
Can't you eat with your mom
for just a couple hours?
I really can't today, Mom.
But I invited Maylin over.
She wants to see you.
I really can't, Mom.
Neen and I are on our way to visit
her grandparents at their country house.
Why didn't you call and tell me first?
I already invited Maylin over.
She'll be so sad that you're not here.
How far away are you?
Can't you drive back now?
Join us for lunch and then go.
You expect her to drive back and forth?
We're already over halfway there.
We don't want to bother going back now.
Wait. You're on speaker?
Yes, Mom. I'm driving.
We can't make it today, Mom.
Please tell that Maylin girl of yours
that if she's so sad,
you'll buy her a lollipop.
Talk to you later.
Runch needs to focus on the road.
You brat. Did you just hang up on me?
Neen, why are you mad at me?
I'm not.
You're lying. I can tell you're mad.
I can explain about Maylin.
So you knew. Why'd you ask then?
You're obviously
- feeling jealous.
- I'm not.
Why would I get jealous?
We're getting divorced anyway.
Maylin is the daughter
of one of my mom's close friends.
We used to play together
when we were little.
That's all. There's nothing more.
Your mom seems to hope for more
since she arranged for you to meet.
Neen.
Don't get upset. Please?
When your grandparents see your face,
they'll be able to tell you're upset.
That'll only make them worried.
They want to see us happy together.
Let's hold hands and head inside.
Grandpa. Grandma.
What brings you here?
I came because
I've missed you both, of course.
Aw,
you're quite the sweet-talker, aren't you?
I've missed you too.
- Me too.
- Let me give her a hug too.
- So impatient, this guy.
- Aw.
You're way too small.
Are you sure you've been eating enough?
Or does Runch want you
to have a model-type body?
I didn't ask her to eat less
so she could have a model-type body.
I've been eating plenty.
Don't worry, Grandpa.
I'm healthy and well.
Runch.
It's been a while.
You're even prettier than I remember.
Thank you.
What about me?
Of course you're the prettiest for me.
How have you both been?
Are you doing alright?
- Yes.
- We've been great.
Grandma asked you what you want for lunch.
Anything is fine.
I'll tell her that.
Wanna go for a walk? It's nice out today.
Sure.
It's been a while
since we last went for a walk.
Before, we used to do it so often.
Okay.
Let's go for a post-meal walk
for our digestion.
You say it's for digestion. But really,
you just want to spend time with me,
don't you?
I know you do.
Let's eat and then
go for a post-meal walk.
Come on.
Do you want to live like my grandparents?
I bet you won't like having to stay here.
I was asking you.
Do you like living that way?
I just like being with you.
You're so full of it.
Flowers for you.
Are you always this cheap
when giving flowers to a girl, gorgeous?
I'm not like you,
Ms. Peeracha Pacharathakul.
You bought an expensive bouquet
of flowers just to congratulate
an Employee of the Year.
You liked it though, didn't you?
Actually…
it did give me mixed emotions.
Congratulations on winning
Employee of the Year.
And the promotion too.
Thank you. How'd you know about this?
Well, my last name is Pacharathakul.
Pacharathakul?
You have the same last name
as Mr. Apichet, my boss.
Yes.
He's my uncle.
It's a beautiful family name, right?
Want to adopt it?
The award and the promotion I got,
you had nothing to do with it, right?
We're not even a couple yet.
Why would I do that?
So if we were a couple, you'd do it?
No.
If you don't believe me, let's become one.
I'm sorry?
I'm asking you to be my girlfriend.
Huh?
Will you be my girlfriend?
I'm sorry, what? Give me a second.
Are you worried?
Well, aren't you?
We've been
getting along great, haven't we?
Well… Yes, we have.
That means we can date, no?
Fine, fine.
I'll give you some time to think.
I'm done thinking.
The answer is yes.
‪Wait.
Enough.
Someone will see us.
Fine.
We can take a rain check.
Next time, I won't hold back.
So you remember?
If it has to do with you,
I'll always remember.
Let's head inside.
My grandparents are waiting
to have lunch with us.
Let's go.
Did I make you blush?
What? Why would I be blushing?
Your face is all red.
It's hot. I'm feeling hot.
Stay here if you want.
What did you do to make
your relationship last to this day?
I don't know how it's done either.
There's no specific method
that can be applied to every couple.
All I can say is,
be patient with each other.
Being patient
may sound like a simple task,
but for some people, it can be difficult.
I agree.
It's complicated
when it comes to
maintaining a relationship.
Your grandma and I
are still together to this day
only because we've been
through so much together.
We've fought.
We've had disagreements.
We've cried more times than we can count.
Your wedding last year
was just the beginning.
Like I said,
be patient with each other.
Being direct but in a patient way
can make big problems small.
Staying patient
is a way to pull yourself together.
Think before you speak or act.
Don't act on your emotions.
It'll only make matters worse.
So, which of you
is more patient?
Probably him.
Because I've been
as intense as fire since I was young.
What makes you more patient then?
It's probably his handsome face.
Same here.
I guess I took after you, Grandma,
because every time I see her pretty face,
I always go soft on her.
Seeing you both like this makes me happy.
I hope you'll love each other
and stay together until you die.
You just need to
move those roses to a pot.
- Can you do that?
- Sure.
I used to buy trees and plant them myself.
But now I have a job,
so I don't have time.
Perfect, then.
I'm counting on you.
- Sure, Grandma.
- Okay.
I never knew you could garden.
In my college years,
I used to love shopping
at the plant market
to buy plants and plant them myself.
But now I have a job,
so I don't have time.
Come here.
Okay.
Do you remember?
White roses are my favorite.
Of course I do.
Do you remember why?
I don't know.
Because they're pretty?
White roses symbolize
a love that is innocent and beautiful
as well as eternal love
and new beginnings.
How cheesy.
Eternal love?
That doesn't exist.
Why are you laughing?
No, I'm not laughing. I'm not.
Wha…
What?
Is there something on my face?
I'll get it for you.
How cute.
You're cute even when your face is dirty.
There. All better.
Get it off completely. Is it all gone?
I'll wash your face after this.
It's all gone now.
Grandpa! Grandma!
Runch and I are done planting the roses.
Can I help you with anything else?
It's huge.
How are we going to wash it?
I know a way.
Hmm?
I didn't know you can wash it this way.
It's pretty fun.
You can let go now.
If I do that, you'll fall.
Let's just keep hugging.
It warms my heart.
Okay.
Oh!
Quick. Take a photo.
Send it. Send it.
HOW'S EVERYTHING, MOM?
There we go.
Did it send, Kae?
We saw it, Mom.
I hope your plan will succeed.
Of course it will.
I'll try my best to make them
change their mind about the divorce.
Surely, this visit
will make them feel something.
We're counting on you, Mom.
We really don't want Neen and Runch
to get divorced.
Yeah, that's right.
Just thinking about it breaks my heart.
I'd understand if they got divorced
because of a conflict.
But they're doing it because of
someone else. I can't accept it.
We don't know what to do either.
When she told us they'd get divorced,
all we could do was listen.
But we definitely don't want that.
But judging from the photo,
if we let them stay there
for two more weeks,
no one will need to push them.
They'll make up on their own.
You can count on me.
Don't you even worry.
I'm sorry. Runch couldn't make it.
She has some urgent work to do.
No worries, Aunt Ging. I understand.
Lawyers have little time to rest.
You're so sweet for understanding Runch.
Well, I've always idolized her
since I was little.
She's just so cool,
no matter what she does.
I even got a law degree because of her.
Runch used to tell me
she wanted to be a lawyer
when she grew up,
and she really did.
That's why I wanted to be like her.
You seem to really like her.
Yes, I do.
Maylin.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
You have a crush on her, right?
Aunt Ging!
You can be honest with me.
These days, it's normal
for women to like women.
I understand.
Yes.
I have a crush on her.
For a while now too.
Help yourself, honey.
Thank you.
Runch.
Come here for a second.
Yes?
Come here.
Neen's taking a shower, right?
Yes, she just got in the bathroom.
Is something wrong?
We have something important to tell you.
Something important?
Her birthday
is coming up in a few days.
Yes, I know that.
We wanted to plan
a surprise for her in advance
here, at our country house.
That way,
we can give her mind and heart a rest.
And she'll get to be happy for real.
It's been a while
since her grandma and I
heard her laugh like she used to.
Please help me out, Runch.
You're the only one
who knows her the best.
Sure, Grandpa, Grandma.
I'll handle everything for you.
Neen is such a lucky girl
to have someone
who loves her so sincerely.
Let's plan it together.
And keep it a secret from her.
Sure.
- This one's really good.
- Thanks.
Have this too.
Neen.
Your grandma and I
are going to an event at the temple.
Can you give us a ride?
Of course. I'll give you a ride.
Please watch over our house, Runch.
You don't have to do much.
Putting away the plates and bowls
would be enough.
Sure, Grandma.
I'll make sure everything's nice and neat.
Perfect. Shall we go
after we're done eating?
- Sure.
- Okay?
Dig in.
Runch.
Runch?
Runch, where are you?
Runch.
What's this about?
In advance of your birthday, Neen.
Make a wish and blow out the candles.
Tonight, your grandparents
won't be coming home.
They're staying at a friend's house.
Yeah. That's what they told me too.
So that means
there will be just the two of us tonight.
Yeah.
So,
what are we doing tonight?
How pretty.
You know,
I've never stargazed here before.
I know.
That's why I wanted
to look at the stars with you tonight.
Did you know?
I used to love stargazing
when I was little.
But now that I'm grown,
I hardly ever look up at the sky.
Whoa!
Runch,
did you see that shooting star?
An actual shooting star--
That's a pretty sunset, isn't it?
3 YEARS AGO
It's nothing compared to you.
You're quite the sweet-talker.
Have you tasted my lips?
How do you know they're sweet?
No, I haven't.
But now I kind of want to.
I wonder if they really are sweet.
Today's our first day as a couple.
May I kiss you?
Lately, Runch and that new girl
seem awfully close.
Today, you made me feel
like you have a secret life
I don't know about.
You punk! You ruined everything!
You're one to talk. What are you doing?
Finding a side chick for your daughter?
I only did it
because I was trying to protect you.
I won't let anyone
hurt my wife's feelings.
No one. Not even you, Mom.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya